const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Which of the following is the laser used for treating posterior capsular opacification in adults?","answers":[{"option":"Nd-YAG laser","bool":true},{"option":"Argon laser","bool":false},{"option":"Excimer laser","bool":false},{"option":"Holmium laser","bool":false},{"option":"Femtosecond laser","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What is the most common type of entropion?","answers":[{"option":"Cicatricial","bool":false},{"option":"Paralytic","bool":false},{"option":"Spastic","bool":false},{"option":"Senile","bool":true},{"option":"Congenital","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What is the drug of choice in primary open-angle glaucoma?","answers":[{"option":"Pilocarpine","bool":false},{"option":"Dipivefrin","bool":false},{"option":"Brimonidine","bool":false},{"option":"Timolol","bool":false},{"option":"Latanoprost","bool":true}]},{"id":3,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Complicated cataracts are complications of which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Phacoantigenic uveitis","bool":false},{"option":"Anterior uveitis","bool":true},{"option":"Diabetic retinopathy","bool":false},{"option":"Phacolytic glaucoma","bool":false},{"option":"Phacomorphic glaucoma","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"A concave lens is used in which of the following conditions?","answers":[{"option":"Isometropia","bool":false},{"option":"Astigmatism","bool":false},{"option":"Myopia","bool":true},{"option":"Hypermetropia","bool":false},{"option":"Anisometropia","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Carbonic anhydrase inhibitors are used in which of the following conditions?","answers":[{"option":"Congenital glaucoma","bool":false},{"option":"Inflammatory glaucoma","bool":false},{"option":"Acute primary angle-closure glaucoma","bool":true},{"option":"Anterior uveitis","bool":false},{"option":"Cataract","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"A man has had an ulcerative lesion on the upper eyelid for over a year. It is diagnosed as a basal cell carcinoma. Which of the following is true regarding this condition?","answers":[{"option":"It is rapidly growing","bool":false},{"option":"It has pedunculated protrusions","bool":false},{"option":"It affects young people","bool":false},{"option":"It is the most common malignancy of the eyelid","bool":true},{"option":"It is a benign tumor of the eyelid","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What is a simple, effective, and long-term treatment for trichiasis?","answers":[{"option":"Bandage contact lens","bool":false},{"option":"Argon laser destruction","bool":true},{"option":"Surgical resection","bool":false},{"option":"Epilation with forceps","bool":false},{"option":"Cold compress","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What treatment is 90% successful in cases of nasolacrimal duct obstruction?","answers":[{"option":"Incision and drainage","bool":false},{"option":"Baloon catheter dilation","bool":false},{"option":"Conservative treatment","bool":false},{"option":"Dacryocystorhinostomy (DCR)","bool":false},{"option":"Probing","bool":true}]},{"id":9,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What is the first-line treatment in acute angle-closure glaucoma?","answers":[{"option":"Pilocarpine","bool":false},{"option":"Brimonidine","bool":false},{"option":"Acetazolamide","bool":true},{"option":"Prednisolone","bool":false},{"option":"Latanoprost","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"According to WHO, blindness is defined as visual acuity of or less than which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Counting fingers only","bool":false},{"option":"6/60","bool":false},{"option":"No perception of light","bool":false},{"option":"6/18","bool":false},{"option":"3/60","bool":true}]},{"id":11,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Which of the following walls of the orbit is most prone to injury?","answers":[{"option":"Lateral wall","bool":false},{"option":"Floor","bool":true},{"option":"Roof","bool":false},{"option":"Posterior wall","bool":false},{"option":"Medial wall","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What is the mechanism of action of a topical carbonic anhydrase inhibitor on the eye?","answers":[{"option":"Contracts pupillary sphincter muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Contracts ciliary muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Increases aqueous outflow","bool":false},{"option":"Decreases aqueous secretion","bool":true},{"option":"Blocks the trabecular meshwork","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What laser does not work on the principle of photocoagulation?","answers":[{"option":"Argon laser","bool":false},{"option":"Infrared laser","bool":false},{"option":"Nd YAG laser","bool":false},{"option":"Visible light laser","bool":false},{"option":"UV laser","bool":true}]},{"id":14,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Atropine acts on what receptors?","answers":[{"option":"Alpha adrenergic","bool":false},{"option":"Opioid","bool":false},{"option":"Nicotinic","bool":false},{"option":"Beta adrenergic","bool":false},{"option":"Muscarinic","bool":true}]},{"id":15,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Trachoma causes which of the following complications?","answers":[{"option":"Ischemia","bool":false},{"option":"Abscess formation","bool":false},{"option":"Hemorrhaging","bool":false},{"option":"Scarring","bool":false},{"option":"Opacification","bool":true}]},{"id":16,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What is the nerve supply of the lateral rectus muscle?","answers":[{"option":"Optic nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Oculomotor nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Abducens nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Trigeminal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Facial nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What is a vision-threatening complication of cataract surgery?","answers":[{"option":"Corneal edema","bool":false},{"option":"Acute endophthalmitis","bool":true},{"option":"Retrobulbar hemorrhage","bool":false},{"option":"Secondary glaucoma","bool":false},{"option":"Wound leakage","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Which of the following is not a part of the retina?","answers":[{"option":"Macula","bool":false},{"option":"Pars plana","bool":true},{"option":"Optic disc","bool":false},{"option":"Rods and cones","bool":false},{"option":"Fovea centralis","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Which of the following is correct on the anatomy of the orbit?","answers":[{"option":"Lateral wall lies at 90Â° to the medial wall","bool":false},{"option":"Optic canal is located in the greater wing of the sphenoid","bool":false},{"option":"The floor is formed by palatine, maxillary, and vomer bones","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior orbital fissure transmits the 4th cranial nerve","bool":false},{"option":"The lamina papyracea is the thinnest part","bool":true}]},{"id":20,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Blunt trauma to the globe would most likely result in rupture of which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Infratemporal limbus","bool":false},{"option":"Supranasal limbus","bool":true},{"option":"Equator","bool":false},{"option":"Infranasal limbus","bool":false},{"option":"Supratemporal limbus","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What is an indication for hyperosmotic agent pharmacotherapy?","answers":[{"option":"Extreme pain","bool":false},{"option":"Acetazolamide is ineffective","bool":true},{"option":"Intraocular pressure below 40 mmHg","bool":false},{"option":"Normal-tension glaucoma","bool":false},{"option":"Inflammatory glaucoma","bool":false}]},{"id":22,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What are the epithelial cells present beneath the anterior lens capsule?","answers":[{"option":"Simple squamous","bool":false},{"option":"Stratified columnar","bool":false},{"option":"Pseudostratified columnar","bool":false},{"option":"Simple cuboidal","bool":true},{"option":"Simple columnar","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Visual impairment is best defined by which of the following statements?","answers":[{"option":"Visual acuity less than 3/60","bool":false},{"option":"Peripheral vision loss less than 30 degrees","bool":false},{"option":"Visual acuity less than 6/60","bool":false},{"option":"Visual acuity less than 6/12","bool":false},{"option":"Visual acuity less than 6/18","bool":true}]},{"id":24,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Which of the following is inappropriate in terms of treating a branched retinal vein occlusion (BRVO)?","answers":[{"option":"Intravitreal anti-VEGF","bool":false},{"option":"Prednisalone","bool":false},{"option":"Methylprednisalone","bool":false},{"option":"Triamcinolone acetonide","bool":false},{"option":"Intravenous acetazolamide","bool":true}]},{"id":25,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Episcleritis is treated with which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Acetazolamide","bool":false},{"option":"Topical steroids","bool":true},{"option":"Mannitol","bool":false},{"option":"Anti-VEGF","bool":false},{"option":"Bevacizumab","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"What is the most conspicuous sign of conjunctivitis?","answers":[{"option":"Increased lacrimation and positive regurgitation tests","bool":false},{"option":"Photophobia","bool":false},{"option":"Mucopurulent discharge","bool":false},{"option":"Erythema due to dilatation of the superficial vessels","bool":true},{"option":"Periocular tenderness upon palpation","bool":false}]},{"id":27,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Which of the following is not used as a vitreous substitute?","answers":[{"option":"Silicone oil","bool":false},{"option":"Expandable gas","bool":false},{"option":"Sterile air","bool":false},{"option":"Ringer's lactate","bool":false},{"option":"Methylcellulose","bool":true}]},{"id":28,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Which of the following is the most dangerous side effect of atropine?","answers":[{"option":"Paralytic strabismus","bool":false},{"option":"Acute angle-closure glaucoma","bool":true},{"option":"Primary open angle glaucoma","bool":false},{"option":"Anisometric amblyopia","bool":false},{"option":"Cataract","bool":false}]},{"id":29,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Terminal bulbs with dendritic ulcers on the cornea occur due to which of the following pathogens?","answers":[{"option":"Adenovirus","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes simplex virus","bool":true},{"option":"Acanthamoeba","bool":false},{"option":"Varicella zoster virus","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes zoster virus","bool":false}]},{"id":30,"info":"4th-year/eye/2017","question":"Arteritic anterior ischemic optic neuropathy is seen in which disease?","answers":[{"option":"Optic disc edema","bool":false},{"option":"Giant cell arteritis","bool":true},{"option":"Papilledema","bool":false},{"option":"Papillitis","bool":false},{"option":"Multiple sclerosis","bool":false}]}]
export default arr